In the not too distant future
somewhere in time and space
Mike Nelson and His robot pals
are caught in in an endless chase
pursued by a woman
who's name is Pearl
an evil gal
who wants to rule the world
she threw a few things in her purse
and in her rocketship
she hunts him all across the universe
[distantly] Pearl: I'll get you!
I'll send him cheesy movies
the worst I can find
la la la
he'll have to sit and watch them all
and I'll monitor his mind
la la la
now keep in mind Mike can't control
where the movies begin or end
la la la
he'll try to keep his sanity
with the help of his robot friends
robot roll call
Cambot!
Cambot: You're on
Gypsy!
Gypsy: Oh stars
Tom Servo!
Tom: Check me out!
Crooooow!
Crow: I'm different
If you're wonderin' how he eats and breaths
another science fact
la la la
just repeat to yourself
it's just a show
I should really just relax
For Mystery Science Theater 3000
Hi everyone. Crow, Servo glad you're here
just got this, uh, notice from Gypsy
apparently she's gotta on the...
main switching unit?
Crow: Huh
Mike: I dunno
so in a couple a minutes
the power's gonna go down
Crow and Tom: Yes!
Mike: Hey, Hey!
Hey. I know what you're thinking
and no looting this time you understand?
[click!]
Crow and Tom: giggling
[SMASH] [BANG]
[giggling continues]
[rummaging]
[click!]
Alright. What you loot?
Crow: Well I broke into my own room
and managed to get away with my TV
he he he
I'll never miss it
Mike: Ha, okay. Tom?
Tom: Ah well. I threw a mannequin
through your window Mike and uh...
Mike: wait wait wait wait
Where'd you get a mannequin?
Tom: Well I keep one for power outages
Anyway. Threw it through your window
managed to get away, uh
your recycling here
I'm not a very good looter am I?
Mike: No. No you're not
Uh, we'll be right back
Crow: If it goes out again I'm grabbing my blender
[theme]
[SMASH]
Mike: Alright. What you loot now?
Tom: Loot?
No no. No looting
I just accidentally dropped an anvil
into your box of commemorative plates
Oh hey look. Pearl's calling
you gonna get that?
Pearl: ...and then I
will rule the world!
That needs a little background
doesn't it
The deal is Smellson
I'm going to rule the world
but you don't rule the world
by going at it all scattershot
Nope
Slow and steady
wins the race old nut
So I'm going to rule the world
but I'm going to do it
One...
Person...
at a time
[thunderclap]
Now who's first?
Brain guy: A mister Todd Gunderson ma'am
Pearl: Ah Gunderson eh?
Tod: Uh. Tod’s fine
Pearl: Tod Tod. Good
well TOD...
whataya say can I rule you?
can I can I? huh? can I?
Tod: Rule me?
Uh no
Pearl: Please?!
Tod: No
Pearl: Grrr!
What if I said I'd kill you
if you didn't let me
Tod: Um. I'm sorry. I really
don't feel that threatened
Pearl: Get out of here
Next!
Brain guy: A mister Tom Servo ma'am
Tom: Hey guys! Here I am
Hey. Glad to help
Mike and Crow: Servo?
Tom: Yep it's me. Heh
Brain guy brought me down
my name was next on the list
totally random!
it's weird
Pearl: So Tom Servo
What do you say?
Can I...
[trails off]
Don't I know you from somewhere?
Tom: It could be.
I do get around
Pearl: The Tom Jones theater
in Branson Missouri
you tried to steal my purse
and I beat you in a...
Tom: No no no no
Must have been some other lucky guy
Pearl: Well. It's not important
Can I rule you?
Tom: Sorry baby
Nobody rules the Tom monster
Pearl: Damn your defences are impenetrable
Brain guy. Send Mike the movie
while I figure out this whole
world ruling thing
Brain guy: Certainly
Mike. Your movie is if
one can measure these things
the worst thing to ever
come out of Canada
It's called The Final Sacrifice
Ma'am may I have the robot?
They need him for the movie
Tom: Go on toots
Take me up curly
Here I am guys
Guys?
[distantly] We're in the theater
Tom: Doh!
Crow: Come on dummy
Tom: Well me?
I don't give a flying Dutchman
about this production
Mike: Huh. I understand everything
up to the word "A"
Crow: He comes from a
long line of Greid Anuses
Tom: [ambiance]
Crow: Hurray. The movie is closed today
because of snow
Tom: You maybe think this
is a documentary about maple syrup?
[ominous drumbeat]
Mike: You brought the face mask you nut
Tom: He's checking his Bioré strip
Crow: I think the movie's going
really well
Mike: Don't worry about me Boss
the hair on my back is keepin me warm
Tom: Beth plus Jason
Crow: Greg Davies?
Mike: Oh man. I dunno. I slept weird
[yawn]
[music intensifies]
Crow: Bigfoot for wrangler relaxed fit
Tom: Randy Bachman is being
pursued by sadomasochists
Tom: [gulping to tempo]
Crow: Hey no fair you guys!
I lost my moon boots
Tom: [gulping]
Mike: My face is warm, but my
shoulders are freezing
Crow: Nobody leaves the
world wrestling federation
Tom: Come back here syrup rustler
Mike: That's his winter tank top
Crow: Canadian rules football
is much different
Mike: Yeah
Tom: I dunno. I'm just happy
Mike: I forgot a mouth hole
Crow: Beethoven's 5th just
can't get started here
Tom: Hi Cindy
[bang]
Mike: He exploded before they could
shoot him
Crow: He changed his name from
I Believe In Something But I Don't Really Go to Church Malcolm
[theme]
Mike: Oh great. The score is skipping
Tom: Oh come on. One more sacrifice
before we go?
Mike: Okay. But this is the Final Sacrifice
Crow: Go away Shane. Go away
Tom: Eh Ron Anderson here
just gotta nip down and make that movie
real good then
Crow: That's an illegal use of
a silent consonant
[Tom hums along]
Mike: You know what? This has the bacony stink
of Canada all over it
Tom: I am ZOMBOR.
kelly
ZOMBOR
[Mike hums along]
Mike: I hope his wooden shoes
get iced up and he crashes
Tom: Yeah
Crow: That's an anagram for
direct to video
Tom: Seven years after the credits?
Mike: I guess
Heh you know what? People are just dyin...
Tom: No.
sorry
Crow: Well I better get back
to my grave
Sun's been up an hour
I'm starting to disintegrate
[somber music]
Tom: He was a good hamster
Hello Dad
Been a long time
and I miss you
I want to know what happened to you
Mike: I died
Tom: What?
Crow: Oh. A mausoleum with a
finished expansion upstairs
[stairs creaking]
Mike: Oh this is where they get
all the stuff to put in TGI Fridays
Crow: How many geeks does it take
to screw in a lightbulb?
Mike: How many?
Crow: Well I dunno
that's why I'm asking you
Tom: Man he's just poured
into that sweater
Mike: This scene was lit by an
itty bitty booklight
Crow: This is where I have secreted away
all my red sweaters
Tom: Oh boy
He's gonna find out his dad
is a rodeo clown
Mike: I don't care if I'm too old
I'm getting my batman pajamas
back outta here
Crow: He was made in the image of
an egg noodle
Tom: Well if I'm going to be a
ventriloquist dummy
I better learn how to live
in this trunk
[Mike grunts with effort]
Crow: Now I'm gonna settle in with
the Book of Mormon
[Tom humming]
Mike: Larry Csonka!
Tom: [sniff]
Oh shouldn't have filed that sandwich
Crow: I've got to find the warranty
on this sweater
Tom: and I will be the one
to hold Larry Csonka down
kiss him so hard
I'll take Larry Csonka's breath away
Mike: Some guys can really
pull off leggings
Crow: I can't wait till they
start the internet
Tom: He's working on his Bud Cort
scrap book
Mike: Ah I'm glad I don't have any friends
'cause then I wouldn't be able
to do this
Crow: Man I'm 25
I hope I hit puberty soon
Mike: I know I’ll call pretending I'm
Bob Griese
Tom: Ah finally
Grandma's head
Mike: No wonder Dad lost all
his money
he invested in lemon mines
Tom: cheerleaders, classmates,
teachers I don't like
Crow: Ah here it is!
The transcript from the
Spassky-Kasparov match of '82
Tom: Devil
living room
den
family room
another devil
To Mike Pipper
Mike: Oh he's a Pipper
wouldn't you like to be a...
Tom: NO
Tom: Ah.
Sex: male. CIM
Crow: It says "do not wrinkle"
Dear Mike
I had a close call today
the cult is on my heels
the map is no longer safe with me
it is the only copy left
the others I have destroyed
we'll meet again soon
be careful, your partner
- Thomas
Mike: Yes there's weight gain powder
in the fridge
Crow: So it's near a Ponderosa Steakhouse
Tom: I'm gonna color it
[theme]
Crow: Morning Larry
Mike: the time is 6 4
Crow: Delayed puberty awareness programs
here
Mike: Man there's an amazing
number of Csonkas
Tom: So we're just watching someone
fritter away their afternoon here
Mike: mhm
Operator: Operator
Hi can I have information please?
Operator: One moment please
Crow: Now that's two moments
I'm sorry
Information: Information
Hi could I have the number for
Mike Pipper?
Mike: No
P I P
P E R
Information: For what city please?
From Eaglehat
Information: One moment
Tom: Eaglehat?
Information: I'm sorry there's no listing
for an M Pipper
Oh okay. Thanks
Crow: and the investigation
comes to a close
Tom: Well I better get to reading my
X-Men comics
Mike: Hey
get this caterpillar off my lip
Tom: Well Larry. I guess I better get going
say hello to Jim Kiick for me
[knocking]
Come in
Crow: Mrs Costanza
What are you studying?
French revolution
Oh that looks more like World War 2
Mike: Oh I'm (???)
Where did you get that?
I found it in the attic
Tom: Leave me alone mom
I'm starting a software company
Well don't work too late
Crow: I'll lock you in as usual.
What was he like?
I thought we talked about this before
I don't want you to cry about what is past
Mike: No emotions. We've discussed that
Is that why you locked up his stuff
in the attic?
you didn't want me to get upset?
You found that?
Troy you had no business there
My father is my business
Tom: Al Lewis as Grandma
Oh Troy I'm sorry
I only want you to forget him
carry on with your own life
Crow: Y'know once you get one
Am I like him?
Mike: No he was masculine and likable
Yes
You're very much like him
Tom: If I'm thinking of the right guy
Crow: Man now my room stinks of Youth-Dew
Tom: MVP, Super Bowl VIII, for Miami
Mike: Seven years later
[engine struggling]
Tom: That’s enough trees for
the
spotted owl, isn’t it?
Crow: Sure
[engine struggling]
Crow: Uh oh. The town's alternator is shot
[engine starts]
Mike: Free pictures of
Brian Mulroney with fill-up
Tom: Oh and who ways there aren't
nice homes in Canada
Oh can you
check it out
[engine struggling]
Crow: Someone's scratching his belly
Damn!
Mike: When it's above 50 or below 40
it never starts
[ominous drumbeat]
Tom: Canada is for lovers
Crow: His truck won't start
but at least his tablecloth is dry
Mike: If you lived here
you’d be in hell by now
Tom: Check out the Linc Hayes topiary
Crow: Hitchcock’s Parade of Homes
Mike: Ah. It's the
Came With the Frame family
Crow: water me
Tom: Hey another kid exactly like
him across town
Crow: He just his exhaustive
four volume biography
of Larry Csonka
[clock chimes 7 o'clock]
Mike: Someone's hitting a fry pan
which means it's 8 o'clock
Tom: Course the clock's set to Miami time
Crow: Well swing choir ain’t
gonna rehearse itself
Mike: Was called in for the night shift
Apparently Aunty never got
laid off after the war
Tom: Why'd he put a laser disc
in the refrigerator?
Mike: Hey. El Santo
Tom: Let’s see if there’s any
Larry Csonka movies on tonight
Crow: Can I discipline you?
[Mike chewing]
Mike: Man. Cold crazy bread
It really is crazy
Tom: Wait...
I haven't read Tolkien
in almost a week
Mike: Script was punched up by Harpo Marx
Crow: Ah. A Yanni song’s about to begin
[suspenseful music]
Mike: What would Coach Don Shula do?
Crow: It’s his Michael Feinstein
signature bat
Tom: TEE-HEE TEE-HEE
Mike: His head is still factory wrapped
Crow: Is he a door to door executioner?
Mike: Ow! I was just gonna
read the meter
Crow: You know it's spring when the
executioners start gettin in the house
[chainsaw]
Tom: It's open. Jeez
Mike: The McCullochs are here
Crow: Can I interest you in a
replacement door?
Mike: Canadian villain Garth Vader
Tom: Icky flakes
Crow: Ah that was a good
seven years
Troy!
I know you can hear me Troy
I know you have the map
I want it
Tom: Jessie “The Body” Ventura
dubbed his voice
Mike: Wow
Aunty sent her
jackbooted thugs to make him lunch
Crow: We just wanna cut your
sugarcane crop
Tom: You thugs.
Don't run with your scimitars
Mike: Damn. He's got a 10 speed
Crow: Get on the banana seat bike
and give chase
Mike: Mh. Let's get out of here
Tom: Hey man. Thank your sister
for sewing our hoods
Mike: and then the drunk guy says
I can't help being an idiot
I'm Canadian
Crow: You're right!
They're so pathetic Mike
[whistle]
Tom: Enough!
There's been too much
Canada bashing
for far too long
I say no more
Mike: Don't you mean no more eh?
Crow: Good one man
they are so stupid
Tom: Stop it now!
Instead let us offer our northern
brothers and sisters
this song of tribute
[music begins]
Oh I wish I was back
in old Canada
a land I which never
shall lampoon
How I pine for the ice covering
Lake Manitoba
and the beauty that is Saskatoon
Mike: I got one
Oh I wish
I was stuck in the hills of Alberta
drinking beer with some big
dumb guy trapping fur
As he scraped and he chiseled all
the moose dung off his boots
I would learn that he's the Prime Minster
Tom: Oh stop that
Crow: Oh I wish I was in
that gave us Peter Jennings
Alanis Morissette
Mike Myers too
No I take that back
I wouldn't go there
even if you paid me
oh Canada you are a
place I must eschew
Tom: Now this is not in the spirit
that I intended
Mike: Oh come on give in
I mean after all they gave us
Edd the Sock
and Rush
Crow: Yeah what are you defending?
they're such feebs
Tom: Okay I'll try
Mike: Alright. Good man
Tom: Oh I wish I was
blowing up Prince Edward Island
And going on to bomb Ontario
The destruction of Canada
and all of its culture
Is by far my fav-o-rite scenario
Mike:  Okay, well that's a little strong
Tom: No, no, you were right Mike
this is much more fun!
Just where the hell does Canada
get off sharing a border
with countries far superior
too it
Crow: Yikes
Why, you lousy, stinking,
francophonic, bacon-loving bastards
Your country's just a giant piece of sh--
Mike & Crow: Whoa! Okay! Whoa! (& etc.)
Tom: I'm sorry
I have no sense of proportion
I'm a disgrace to my uniform
Mike: No that's, that okay
now calm down now
mustn't hate
Crow: At least so overtly
Mike: Exactly right
must disguise our hate
just a little.
Alright we'll be right back
Shhhh, shhh. It's okay now, Dudley
Calm down...calm down
Tom: Pardonnez-moi...pardonnez-moi
[theme]
Mike: Ah. Seven years later
[engine struggling]
Tom: Dental hygienist of the week
Crow: Yeah once he gets it started
he's gonna drive it to the front yard
take a couple a tires off
and let it rust next to
the old freezer
sitting on the front lawn
[engine revving]
Mike: In my work for a bloodthirsty cult
I depend on my Gran Torino
Crow: I think his menace is undercut
by the baby on board tag
Tom: Yeah I think your cameraman
is stuck in the door
Mike: Can you imagine how many Potato Olé
containers are on the floor of that car?
[cheerful music]
Tom: This music is really more suited to
plate spinning
Kind of a mazurka
Crow: I'm losin track of the
crappy vehicles here
Mike: Crank the Molly Hatchet and let’s roll!
Tom: I'm Sherry
[engine revs]
[radio in background]
Mike: Now I have to listen to As It Happens
Tom: Honk honk! On your ass!
Crow: Oh, I love trash, ahhhh oww
[jaunty music]
Tom: Maybe it's the cheap
Canadian gas they're using
just can't get up any speed
Mike: Damn you, Pee-wee!
Tom: Hi! I'm Billy the building!
Mike: Unfortunately the truck is
making a delivery
right back to the cult
Crow: Well, let’s just go get some
bullwhips and pose for Mapplethorpe
Mike: Yep
[Crow singing along]
Tom: Huddled in a pile of dirty laundry
just like home
Mike: It sounds like video poker music
Crow: And they take refuge in the
Anne Murray National Forest
Tom: Beautiful isn't it?
I think he’s the Tin Drum kid
Mike: He's the kind of clown
who puts $1.87 of gas in his truck
Crow: Help me, oh Saint Larry Csonka
Tom: Well. Went further
than it usually does
Mike: Like a [cough] rock
[bang!]
Tom: Another human being.
Oh I'm in for a beating
What the hell?
Crow: I've always been back here,
remember?
What are you doin back there kid?
I...
Tom: I'm laundry
I needed, uh
a ride
Mike: Is he a makeup-less clown?
Why don't you get in the cab
it's much more comfortable there
Crow: Actually I bet it isn't
Tom: So... uh. eh then, eh?
Mike: Don't you love our
health care system?
Here. Put this on
Crow: It's made of lunch meat
Thanks
[Tom hums the theme]
Know anything about motors?
No sir
Not really
Tom: I know all the songs from
Once Upon a Mattress, though
Let's have a look
Mike: Are you going to be a Mountie or
a fishing guide when you grow up?
Where are you heading?
Crow: Liquor store
Looks like I'm headin nowhere
Oh I see the problem
the gas line is loose
You're gonna be behind the
steering wheel and
crank her over when I tell you
Tom: He’s wearing fashions by Mac Davis
Mike: I'll just uh
pour my garbage in here
Now!
Tom: Kaboom!
[engine struggling]
Crow: Didn’t Barbara Mandrell have
hair like his at one point?
Tom: I think so
yeah, yeah
Put the pedal all the way down!
Mike: Hmm. Dare I?
[engine struggling]
Tom: Better check this oil here
Yep. 10W-30
Crow: ooh is hair is on fire
[engine roars to life]
Mike: Okay bring the brats out
Tom: Out with my truck again
Whats the name laddie?
Troy McGreggor
I'm Rowsdower
Zap Rowsdower
Crow: Well my name's Bilge Schtinkwater
Mike: Rowsdowermobile. Away!
Tom: and together they fought crime
throughout southwestern Alberta
Crow: So Rowsdower
Is that a stupid name... or?
Uh, fill her up
You stay here and I'll her you
a chocolate bar, okay?
Mike: Buy me anything in there with
Larry Csonka on it. I’ll pay for it
Crow: Oh shoot. I'm in Canada
Operator get me the police
Mike: and the cops pick their
Zap Rowsdower hotline
Yes, Officer. I found this kid
in the back of my truck
Crow: And Play is in the front seat
Tom: Go on, big mama, the highway
Why should I know? Ask him
Crow: Ew. Gotta get this dead woodchuck
out from under the seat
Look you gonna send someone
to pick him up?
Mike: What. Do they think they’re in Idaho?
Crow: Hey I've got 89 cents
worth of cans back there
Zap Actionsdower
Mike: My hood wicks moisture from my face
[gunfire]
Crow: Um, eat my dust?
Tom: Do these pants go with
this sweater?
[gunfire]
Mike: You know he blends in
he looks like a sack of garbage
Crow: This is no time for zymurgy
Tom: Eh just don't shoot at me for a
couple of minutes, okay? Thanks
Mike: If this doesn’t work I’ll throw
balls of carp dough
Crow: You want us to pick that
up for you?
Tom: I knew there was an upside
to being an alcoholic
Mike: Will you take those to recycling?
Thanks!
Crow: Canadian Mannix!
Mike: So...
You wanna hit the breaks there or not?
Tom: Oh I'm so relaxed right now
[theme]
Rowsdower
I can explain
Those men were trying
to kill me
Mike: Yeah, tell it to my acid
washed jeans
[fire crackling]
You have any idea what kind of
people you're dealing with?
Crow: They’re from Saskatchewan
No
It's a cult
Tom: They worship blue oysters
They wanna rule the world
How do you know that?
I've been around kid
Crow: and I've been a
square kid
Tell me more about them
Tom: Their faces are
lumpy and whiskered
oh wait that's me
Their race ruled this land once
Mike: They ruled one acre for about a week
Nobody knew
The race of the Ziox civilization
Crow: Isn’t that a sandwich cookie?
Dad wrote about them!
Crow: BTO was such a great band, man
Look
Mike: I'm about to puke kid
You might want to clear out
Look at the writing
Ancient!
Tom: Old as the crumbs in your mustache
Where does this lead to?
Well, nobody knows for sure
Except my dad
but um
Crow: I disappointed him
He was killed seven years ago
and I wanna know why he died
this map is my only lead
Mike: Yeah hang on [burps]
Go to sleep kid
I'm taking you home in the morning
Tom: Oh. I think he's taking him
home in the morning
Rowsdower
Yeah?
Crow: Why do I feel like having haggis?
Have you always been a
Mike: Hopeless drunk?
A drifter?
Tom: Rowsdower? Could you put out my head?
No
What were you before?
Crow: Well I used to give plasma
you might know me from that
I was uh
Mike: A Chippendales dancer
A businessman
What happened?
Tom: Well I switched to beating
up annoying kids with beer bottles
Go to sleep kid
Crow: Your harshin my buzz
Mike: Now is this touching or boring?
I can't...
Rowsdower
Tom: Now that is a darling maxi skirt
Crow: Rowsdower
Mike: Dreamt I was stuck with a chunky
chunky backwoods looser
named Rowsdower
Ah!
Crow: I think my voice changed overnight
Good morning
So you gonna get us out of here?
I'll get us out of here
Crow: Then we'll stall 50 yards
down the line
Why were you gonna turn me
over to the cops?
'Cause I like to keep my nose clean
Mike: My body suffers for it, but
Helping a runaway kid can get
me in big trouble
Tom: I'd love for you to meet the
people of my youth group
Rowsdower
Crow: Have you ever bathed?
Will you help me find what's
behind the map?
Mike: Oh I don't go map finding behinding
You should be in school
Not running around
hunting down lost civilizations
Besides
the map could be a fake
Fantasy of your old man's
Why do you think those men were
following us yesterday?
Crow: They thought I was that guy
from Due South
Don't you see?
They were after this
Tom: Rowsdower's got one of
screendom's best rear ends
You can be a handout kid
Mike: Rowsdower!
Crow: Do you know how fast
you were going Rowsdower?
Come on
Come on baby. Don't let me down
Tom: I won't Rowsdower
Watch out kid
Mike: Rowsdower-er-er-er-er
Damn
You're gonna drive
while I push at the front
Start out slow
when you get up some speed
floor her. got it?
Crow: And I’d like to thank Dan Aykroyd
for doing that last line
Go!
Tom: Fudge
Mike: Children and pregnant
should not watch this scene
You know in fact no one really
should watch any of these scenes
Crow: This is like when our nursing home
volunteer bus broke down
[bang!]
wow!
Tom: Sounds like Rowsdower's
heart just exploded
[Mike panting]
I don't think that was a very good idea
Shut up
We're in for a long walk
We're gonna walk?!
Well it's not my fault
You're the one that got us
into this mess
You stay here while I go get us
some water
I'll go
Crow: Can you carry me?
Canteen's in the cab
Tom: And the cabs at Columbus and 77th
Mike: If you find a package store
get me some Yukon Jack
Crow: Thanks for the ride mister
Tom: Well I try to work out
but it just gets hard
Mike: Getting water for Rowsdower
Rowsdower wants me to get water for him
Tom: [sniffing]
Ew nature smells
Crow: Mike is there any way I could hop
into the movie
and dump this kid's books?
Mike: Somebody covered their tomato plants
Crow: Let’s see what my Cap’n Crunch
treasure map says
Mike: Three baguettes
Tom: Rowsdower Rowsdower
Rowser-Rowser Rowsdower
Bowsa-Bowsa Lowsdower
Sobbity-Sobbity Sowsdower
Bippity-Boppity Bowsdower
Bobity-Dobity Dower Rows
dower
Crow: Somebody's breaking
shredded wheat biscuits
Mike: Okay I dropped the canteen
and I got lost
Right on schedule
Crow: Ah next I have to fall,
break my ankle, be attacked by coyotes,
and buried by a bear
Crow: Take a left at the tree
That helps
[theme]
[Bobo whimpering]
Pearl: Bad news losers
We won't be in today
'cause Bobo ate a bad can of
Canadian bacon
and he came down with hockey hair
and now we've all got it
Bobo: Lady? Lady?
Can I watch Power Rangers?
Mike: Well, gee Pearl
that's too bad. I guess that means
it's contagious?
Pearl: Oh I'm sure you guys will be fine
I mean we live with the ape
so when he gets hockey hair
we all get hockey hair
don't worry
The doctor says I have to
have more Whoppers
and malted milk balls
Pearl: Yes, yeah yeah, yes
Tom: Oh for cryin out...
It's an airborn virus. Sheesh!
Crow: Mike what's your deal?
How come you don't have it?
Mike: Oh I had it once already
from uh 1982 to 1992
Once you get it once you
can't get it again
Pearl: Oh no you guys got it too huh?
Well the best thing is to just
let it run its course
Brain guy: Well I think it's great
I've never felt so masculine
I feel like Guy Lafleur
Bobo: It's time!
For my hourly Ben and Jerry's
Crow: Huh I have this intense
craving for Zubaz
Mike: Yeah you're gonna get that
Crow: Oh movie sign!
Tom: Oh Sherrie
Mike: Sorry you guys
Troy!
Crow: It's the Canadian Nick Nolte
Troy where are you?!
Tom: Mr. Aikman?
Mike: Hey mister. Have you seen Rowsdow...
Ah yay
Come here
What?
What I found
What is it?
It's a tunnel!
Yeah right
Crow: Teh. That is a classic Rowsdowerism
Tom: A bug. Yuck
Mike: You're gonna throw me
down there aren't ya
Tom: No matter where he goes
he finds a basement to dwell in
Mike: 'scuse me
Wow!
Tom: These are really cheap sets
[lighter clicks]
This tunnel must be dug
hundreds of years ago
Tom: I sensed that with my hair
My hair is an elaborate network
of nerves constantly
processing information
This tunnel is on the map!
I was right
Map is real
Mike: Map Israel?
I believe Israel has been fairly
well mapped already
Crow: It’s an evil Porky Pig
Mike: The Puking Buddha
Crow: Bletch! I hate, bleh!
What is that? I have hair in my mouth
Blehh!
Tom: Woah not there kid.
Sensitive area
Mike: Never climb in people
you don't know
[clang]
Troy?
Crow: Are you dead? 'cause if you are
I'm gonna take off
Mike: Firewood for sale!
Tom: Guess they thought he was
a baby harp seal or something
Mike: The just about to sneeze god
[water dripping]
Wow!
Crow: I really don't understand
[guns cocking]
Mike: He trespassed on
Charlton Heston’s place
Tom: We bagged our own heads and saved
Crow: Give up your hockey hair!
Mike: Never!
You!
So you've not forgotten me Rowsdower
We meet again
For the final time I'm afraid
Tom: Red Grooms’ Dracula
[water dripping]
Crow: My Hawkwind album cover will help
Mike: Nope nothin. I don't get it
Tom: Hey come on kid. Give us
a hearty "Rowsdower"
Dad
Crow: That’s my favorite Jack Lemmon movie
You were here
Weren't you
Where's the boy?
Mike: Could you squat down?
I was tryin to get you in the face actually
The boy Rowsdower
Tom: The boy
He went into the cave with you
and has the map
I want it
I don't know!
Tom: Look into your heart, eh?
Crow: We're gonna make you drink
something other than beer
Mike: It’s a cult that worships
Georgia O’Keeffe
Tom: Hey look! Milk Duds. They never go bad
Crow: His arm sinks in up to the elbow
Mike: Now give me your lunch money
Tom: Look at that
Look at what you did . Look
Crow: He could easily be in Lynyrd Skynyrd
You don't control me
This has controlled your entire life
you broken fool
Mike: Ayy, bra strap
You're crazy!
No I'm not crazy
I shall see the world
ruled by the only race that was
created in perfection
There will be no place for the weak
The ugly
Vermin like you
Go to hell!
Crow: Or at least Edmonton
Our day of conquest is oncoming
Mike: I’m sorry, what did you say
about Burton Cummings?
What do you mean?
That is why you came back isn't it?
Tom: You left your albums at my place
On a day soon
An hour of darkness
Our god will will accept a human sacrifice
Mike: Or you. I'm kidding
This warm depth
Will provide me with an
army of invincible warriors
Crow: He’s got a goiter
Legions of lost souls
trapped deep beneath the Earth
will rise from their grave
and side with me
Crow: You use too much mousse
Shall rule the world
Take him out into
the woods and kill him
Mike: And take away his blow comb
Spread out and find the boy!
Tom: Sir uh. Should we pick a place
to meet back, or...
I guess not then. Okay
Mike: Yep
Crow: The ancient civilization's
toilet keeps running
[water dripping]
Mike: A treasury of
Sergio Aragonés sketches
Tom: Cool
Oh I will have this painted on the side
of my van some day
Crow: You, uh, got a preference about
where you'd like us to kill ya eh?
Mike: No tomorrow is casual day
I think I'm gonna wear a yellow t-shirt
Tom: Ah! I have escaped [yells]
Crow: Cripes. He rolled out of bounds
Mike: Oh what is this obsession
with not showing us
who's getting into what truck?
Tom: Must get a funny tan line
Crow: Oh no, they’ve got a Chevy!
They’re so dependable!
Tom: Quick climb a tree
Trucks can't climb trees
Mike: ooh. You know if you hit a Rowsdower
you get to keep it
Crow: The meat's a bit gamey
but it's good for sausage
Tom: I'm okay. Want to try again?
Crow: Grass stains
When you have cults
you’ve got to have Tide
Mike: Dear Counselor Troi
I waited at Denny’s
but you didn’t meet me
Tom: Dear Agent Scully,
did not appreciate your lawyer’s tone
Crow: And so it is with a heavy heart
that I must resign from chess club
Where are token crosses
The city is located
Mike: Man, I solved Myst in
ten minutes, why can’t I do this?
Tom: This is a passive sentence
I'd better alert my English club
Mike: Back! Back you silverfish! Back!
Crow: I can see why Quebec wants
to be separate from all this
Mike: He was raised by
a family of moles
Tom: Wait. I have an appointment
to get beat up
Mike: Look like a twig
Well that shouldn't be hard
Crow: Sir you have a hole in your shoe...
Oops ooh shh shh
Mike: He's built like a
woman phy ed teacher
Tom: My shirt is charcoal
That's basically black
Crow: This is just like when they bury
me every week at school,
and give me pink belly, and
hang me from the goal post,
and shave my head, and magic marker
my weenie, and stuff me in my locker
[Tom imitating a monkey]
[bang]
Mike: I must slip back and
sell candy bars for band
Tom: I'm just a bush
You may want to pan off me
Crow: What the? Hey, I had
a bead on a goose. Eh
Tom: Eh!
Eh
ehhhh
[gunfire]
Mike: Gil, no!
Not Étienne
[gunfire]
Crow: I'm in no particular hurry
The Cults got their schedule I got mine
Tom: Hey are they after me?
[gunfire]
Mike: Zut alors, je suis mort
Tom: ey, boys in the hoods
Mike: Oh, man
Crow: Drop dead
Crow: Mike? Would you say these guys
are in a heavily forested area?
Mike: Uh, yeah, sure
Crow: Would you call these
the deep woods?
Mike: Yeah
Crow: Because, because when
you’re in the deep woods you can’t
beat the reliable, reasonably
priced mosquito repellant “Off.”
Mike: Huh
Crow: Man, you never even
saw that coming, did ya?
Mike: Wait it's me!
Tom: I know.
Crow: Ah they're eloping
Mike: Uh, uh. This is just like
when I almost missed my
“Teens Encounter Christ” bus
[both panting]
Crow: Come on. It was like
30 yards
Tom: Yeah my hair's a mess
So what?
You were one of them?
Mike: An uncooked bratwurst with hair
[Tom panting]
I was
Crow: I was only part time
[gasp] and then I got laid off
Years ago
Why?
Tom: Let me die first then
I'll tell you
[Tom breathing heavily]
It started with the nightmares
[Tom imitating heartbeat]
The drums
They were calling me
Mike: Wow nobody ever calls me
Was Satoris. He started it all
How?
He's psychotic
Too many people underestimated him
and died mysteriously
Tom: Hold on. I'm havin a series
of elaborate heart attacks
Is that how my father was killed?
Tom: I'm not telling
I don't know
Tom: Ah! Now its turned into a stroke
Satoris found out I
was only a half blood
Soon after he threw me out
I... [hears noise in distance]
Mike: Ope. It's just a jackalope
Let's get outa here
This way
Crow: That's a little too much
decolletage for me
Crow: Ahh. Any given weekend in Canada
Mike: Sides of his heart are
blowing out like old tires
[pew, pew!]
Crow: Rowsdower!
[Tom gasping for air]
Mike: This is fun!
Crow: They’ve stumbled upon
Geddy Lee’s birthplace
Okay
Guess we've had it
Crow: I probably only had about
three more months anyway
Not yet
Mike: It’s the Wizard of Id biathlon
Tom: Hey, it looks like their
tiiiin roof
rusted
Crow: Alright Abraham Lincoln
Stop writing on that damn shovel
and come out with your hands up
Mike: Oh this is no big deal
It's how I get through every school day
Tom: Winnipeg confidential
[floors creaking] [loud rummaging]
Crow: I should tell you that I wheeze loudly
when I'm scared
[Crow wheezes]
Mike: Ah Guillaume this is my place
Would you mind?
Crow: Man, they're bound to smell me
[footsteps]
Crow: Ah, merde, mon pied
Mike: Damn. Broke a heel
Crow: Guy upstairs had bad enuresis
Tom: I've been pulling Ziox
double shifts all week
it's killing me
Mike: I haven’t been this tense
since mock U.N
Crow: Is it possible to trash
a garbage house?
[crows cawing]
Mike: This was Grandma's hunting shack
[caw!]
Crow: It’s Heckle!
Tom: No, it’s clearly Jeckle
Crow: Oh, you're right
Crow: They shot a pair of snowshoes
and had them stuffed and mounted
FOOD!
Crow: Yeah no beer through
Tom: More FOOD!
What the hell are you doing here?
Crow: We were eating your FOOD
Against the wall!
Mike: It’s Gordon Lightfoot at home
Cult leader send you here
to spy on me?
Know of him?
Get 'em up! Get 'em up!
[gun clicks]
We have your ??? all over this place
[stammering] No... It's not about...
w-w-we just escaped from him
Then what's that there mark doing
on your shoulder there
A long story
McGreggor tell him
McGreggor?
Troy McGreggor
Crow: It must hurt
Thomas' son?
Yeah!
Do you know him?
Tom: Know him?
He was delicious!
[theme]
Name's Pipper
Mike Pipper
Tom: Pipper!
Your dad and me were partners
in archeology
Mike: Pipper partner
Many digs we did together
Mike: Pipper digs
Good man he was your dad
Always laughing
Stubborn though
Crow: Another helping of filth for you?
What happened to him?
Mike: I jerked him
I'll tell you
The last year
Your father and I were together
We was searching for a...
lost civilization
Ziox civilization?
That's right
We made calculations as to
where the remains of
their city might be located
That's when we ran into Satoris' cult
Tom: By the way, I hates dat rabbit
They wanted our information
Thomas was too stubborn
So they killed him
Mike: Could I drink him? No
Plant here
This was one of our base camps
Lived here ever since
What do you know about Satoris?
Understand him
You must know about the Ziox
Crow: Ziox now with Lapatiphomene
Now, thousands of years ago
long before the Indians
This land was inhabited by the Ziox
Tom: No it wasn't
They were a highly intelligent race
Far past us in...
science, and architecture, and literature
Tom: No they weren't
They built a huge city
Tom: No they didn't
Far greater than anything the
old Romans or Egyptians
had ever known
The buildings were covered
in gold and silver
Crow: Matted hair
In the center they built a temple
To, um
praise their god
Mike: Then they put a bottle brush
down my throat
It's all gone now
Erased from existence
How?
Tom: No no. Don't encourage him
Here's a mystery
As the legend goes
There was a period of great wealth
Brought discontentment to the people
People began to fear
Crow: Mmm. Good dope
Fear brought superstition
So they build an idol
Well
Their god cursed them and flooded the land
with a rainstorm that lasted
a full month
Mike: Their basements got wet
Soil became so soft
city sank into a huge quagmire
Crow: Wait I'm a huge quagmire
Survivors were
doomed to roam the Earth
That's why this cult is
all that's left of them
Mike: Hey what's this a pile of?
Oh, "crap." That's right
Satoris believes in the idol
He thinks that by sacrificing
someone too it
It'll provide him with an invincible army
that can conquer the world
Except that if the idol is ever destroyed
the old city will return to
it's former glory
As a symbol of good
Would mean the end to Satoris' power
Uh these are all legends of course
Wait a minute
Tom: I have a gag in my pocket
Look
Tom: Oooh! What is that?
Gimme that, varmint
Your father made this
Tom: Didn't do a very good job
I saw the original in a secret chamber
not far from here
We know
I translated the sentence with
the help of my father's notes
Where are token crosses...
the city is located
What does it mean?
Tom: It means,
“Oooh, I’m gonna hog-tie that varmint.”
Crow: He's playing connect the gods
Tom: Come and sit by my side if you love me
so I hasten to bid me adieu
Ooooh!
Crow: Oooh! I needs an eraser
Mike: Here's the plan. My army of
trained rats will lead the charge
and my scabies will protect
our flank
Tom: Well?
Crow: Pipper cam
It's the symbol
Tom: Emperor Haile Selassie
Where the lines cross is
the exact location of the city
And the idol?
Tom: Oooh, I hates those questions
I don't know what you're thinking
Me and Thomas searched and found nothing
The idols a legend
Tom: I hates legends
[old prospector noises]
..dead and gone for more than
a thousand years
But the cult is alive
Yeah the cult is alive
But its beliefs are based on legends
In time the cult leaders will
find out themselves
cult will gradually be dissolved
And how many lives will it claim
before this happens?
Go home
Forget about the cult
Don't let it destroy your life too
It already has
Crow: Look at my hair!
Tom: Wait. I was gonna sing something from
Bone Machine
Crow: If it’s any consolation
I hates that rabbit too
Mike: Well. Who's up for a moose lip omelet
Old Proset man
I remember him
He was with Satoris the
night your father was killed
Tom: There's the door. I can just leave
You don't mean that...
Killed your father?
Crow: Sounds fun, but I'm busy
I don't know
Mike: Well, how about a game of Balderdash?
Tom: Ooooh! Fresh towels in the guest room
Crow: Nothing? Absolutely nothing?
Tom: Nope sorry Crow
but from everything I've read here there's
nothing we can do about hockey hair
You just have to get plenty of
rest and hockey
and let it take care of itself
Crow: Alright
Tom and Crow: Woah, Mike!
Mike: Hey guys
Tom: Mike, what happened to you?
Mike: Oh I'm just seeing what
it's like to smoke a pipe
Crow: No no no. It's your hair!
It's like, uh. It's...
Mike: Ahh!
Woah! Holy cow
Tom: Don't panic now Mike
you've simply got a case of
grizzled old prospector syndrome
Not surprising. It is associated with
immunity to hockey hair
Crow: Yeah it may not even be
a full blown infection
Unless you've been saying consarn it a lot
Mike: Nope consarn it can't
Oh! Dagnabbit
Oh well fiddlesticks
Little varmints. I guess I am hornswaggled
Welp. What do you reckin I
should do about it?
Tom: Well see, uh...
Nothin to do Mike. You just
gotta let it run its course
Crow: Yeah you'll want to
pan for gold probably
you'll probably buy a mule
Mike: Well, wonder how I picked it up
Tom: Well let's see
you been kissing any prospectors?
Mike: Nope
Hold on wait a minute
No. No I haven't
No, you know what?
That was a surely truck farmer
Darn fine kisser though
Crow: You old coot
We'll be right back
[theme]
Crow: dagnabbit
Tom: Cleared right up
Mike: Oh language camp is so far away
I'm taking you home tomorrow
Tom: I know Mom and Dad
will just love you
Troy!
Mike: Man, you kill one guy's Dad
Crow: I wonder if there's
beer on the sun
Mike: Ah, crusty pants, a filthy wall
Good morning
Crow: Oh man those 12oz curls really
take it out of me
Tom: Have a drink on me tattoo
Crow: Leif Garrett today
Mike: Well that's enough for one day
Tom: Val-der-ee, Val-der-ah-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Mike: Man that's a terrible
golf stroke
Crow: I'll plant the roses here
Tom: Bleh!
Ahh!
Euhhh!
Hiss!
Mike: He's layin on a bear
Crow: Hey he got to second
base with himself
Tom: Well I got that done
Crow: God bless Mommy, and Daddy,
and Grandpa, and all my evil henchmen
Mike: Ahhrgh, oh, another M.I.
Tom: Oh great
Mike: He’s invoking the powers of Bryan Adams
Tom: One!
Tom: Bonanza
Crow: Oh I'm exhausted
I gotta take a nap after
I'm done sleepin
Tom: Bless my stick, oh holy Willie Mosconi
Mike: Oh man. That's not a nose
That's a duplex
Tom: Ah this'll teach me
Mike: Hand me my top hat
Tom: Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo
doodly-doo-doo-doo!
Crow: Charge!
Crow: Alrighty the doctor will be
in to see you in just a minute
Mike: Aww. Your s'more fell in
[Tom and Crow chanting]
Crow: I got ketchup on my hand!
Tom: Well I'm not hiring these people
to do my nipple piercing
Mike: I forgot the liquor stores close at 8!
Tom: Sorry!
Troy?
Troy!
Crow: Now Mike, technically that paper is
s-s-smokin’!
Tom: No.
Mike: Kramer-dower
They took him
Tom: Well I gotta go work out
Why?
Mike: Ah man. My lice has left my beard
A lone boy
[whinnying]
Crow: Had a hard time saddling up
the Mrs today
Mike: Made you some trail mix
out of rat droppings and hair
She's old
but she got lots of spirit
Tom: Now ride, postman!
I'll climb on and come with you
No
It's too slow
But thanks for everything
Crow: The fleas and all. Y'know
Head north 'till you get to the river
Follow it upstream
Mike: The Lone Rowsdower
Crow: Yeah, yeah, I know the routine
now the double jock-lock
Tom: Oh goody. You're gonna
ride back here with me!
You guys know any camp songs?
Mike: Ah sir?
You know maybe if you got rid of that
huge gunny sack of ground pork and...
Oh that's your butt. I'm sorry
Crow: 'scuse me a moment
Tom: Why couldn’t I have been bought
by a seventh-grade girl?
Mike: Hang on. Now it's my
turn to ride you
Crow: Ladies and gentlemen
Mr. Alan Jackson
Tom: Erich von Stroheim
hitches across America
Mike: My glee club will be
looking for me
And for your friend Rowsdower
I hope he's not late
Else we shall have to start without him
He'll be here
Stop you!
Crow: You, you pusses make me laugh
I like you Troy
'tis a pitty you have to die so soon
You are so much like your father
Bright
Stubborn
Tom: Well suborn anyway
and in my way
Mike: Hang on. I gotta tinkle
Who killed my father?
Why don't you ask your friend
when he arrives?
Crow: Ha ha! The jokes on you
I don't any friends
Mike: Hey. How'd he get his
pants clean?
Tom: Say what you want about the
filthy grizzled guy
He does a good load of laundry
Crow: You got mud on your face,
you big disgrace,
shoving those sandwiches into your face,
singing “We will, we will Rowsdower!”
Sing it!
We will
we... will
Rowsdower
Crow: I guess that's over
Mike: Hello? Have you seen the
other hooded thugs?
Crow: Ah he splashed around
a little thug musk
in the area to lure them
[bang]
Mike: Oh I shot right in-between them
I got confused
Tom: Balanchine!
Crow: Gérard go that way
Robert follow me
Crow: Michael, Gerry help me!
Mike: Smell my fingers!
Crow: A horse! My six-pack for a horse!
Tom: It turns out to be Mount Pinatubo
they all fall in. The end. Bye!
Mike: No no no no
No you don't junior
Get in here
[all breathing heavily]
[theme]
Mike: Oh, wow, it’s a Stuart Anderson’s
Cattle Company cult
Keep quiet
Crow: My Rowsdower has come for me
Tom: Mammy!
Crow: I’m just remembering
a scene from Bio-Dome
Cut yourself loose
Hurry up
Mike: I dropped it
My men will not disturb us
They're closing off all avenues of escape
Crow: Don’t worry, we won’t hurt you
You fear me
Perhaps you will remember
your last defeat
Ahhh!
Tom: Hey. I wasn't done
[whack]
Crow: What is this?
A grappling hook dumping ground?
Tom: Fire better not get near his mousse
Mike: Which is the sharp side?
Crow: Hey, this is it!
This is the actual
Crazy World of Arthur Brown
Mike: Um. I cut both my wrists
Seven years ago you fought me
trying to save Thomas McGreggor
Now you fight to save his son?!
Crow: Well you started it
You killed him and left me alive
determined for the rest of my life
McGreggor refused to cooperate
He had to die
You will (???) a crime much worse than his
You broke the sole law of our society
You left
Death will be too merciful for you
Zap Rowsdower
I chose to do this
To torment you by our drums
To the end of your miserable life
Mike: I somehow swallowed the knife
Crow: And I'm really mad that
you never do the dishes
when it's your turn
Mike: Oh, nice. Are those Totes?
Oh, hey, they are
You are mine
[bang]
Tom: Ow!
You shot my butt
What the hell? You shot me in the butt!
You will be the last sacrifice
[gun loading]
Last one between me
and ultimate power over the Earth
Mike: Oh wait. There's one guy after you
so you're second to last though
Crow: So Mike. Most humans when you
shoot 'em in the butt they
burst into flames?
Mike: Well... I dunno
Crow: Can we try it? Turn around
You alright kid?
Tom: Well I don't have many friends,
girls don't like me, and my teachers absolutely ha--
Oh oh yeah. I'm fine
[thunder]
Mike: Somewhere Lee Trevino
scurries for cover
Tom: moooooooo!
[crash]
The legend goes
If the idol is ever destroyed
the city will return to its former glory
It's a symbol of good
and will mean the end of Satoris
Mike: And remember,
if the ladies don’t find you handsome,
at least you should be handy
Crow: Stay with me Troy and I'll guide you
in the ways of alcohol cigarettes, and meat
Tom: Well was a pretty good cult
but hockey season is starting and all
Crow: Okay hood washing time guys
Mike: Let's just do them all in one load
They're all the same color
Tom: So Dad. You think we're gonna
get payed for this week?
Crow: Somebody reboot the kid
Mike: The Love Canal State Forest
[cracking]
Crow: Hey I'm in a snowmobile club
with that one guy
Tom: Rowsdower
Mike: So their city is a
pop-out greeting card
Tom: It's not actually a lost city.
It was just unclaimed
Mike: Rowsdower
Crow: Wow. It’s Expo 67
Tom: Rowsdower
Mike: A whole 'nother city to fail in
Tom: I wonder if they need
snow plowin services
Mike: Audrey Hepburn! Oh, it’s Troy
Crow: Well son of a buck. That just
flew up there
Tom: Luke. It is your destiny
Crow: Susan Dey! Oh, no, it’s Troy
Tom: He’s going to turn into a war-wilf
Mike: How 'bout a smoke, kid?
Tom: Hey the neosporin really worked
Alright!
Crow: My drinkin arm is healed!
Mike: Rowsdower you're squeezing my
Mike: Row-Rowsdower, Row
Crow: That shot contains too much nostril
Tom: Heck. I can't believe the ancient
city kicked us out already
Mike: Join us next week when
Troy and Zap
battle an army of evil Acadian
robots on Cape Breton
Crow: Then in upcoming weeks
they’ll take on a band of zombie
fur trappers in Medicine Hat
Mike: That’s on Zap and Troy:
The Legendary Journeys
[Tom singing]
Tom: Oh baby Rowsdower
saves us
and saves all the world
Crow: He comes to save the day in a broken truck
Mike: With a stinky denim jacket
on his back
Crow: He couldn't help this movie
which really sucked
Mike: But at least we didn't
have to see him play hacky sack
Crow: What?
Mike: I'm sorry. I panicked
Tom: Well wake up!
This is important to me damn it
Mike: Well I'll try to do better
Tom: Here it comes. Listen
Rowsdower saves us
and saves all the world
Mike: Rowsdower saves us
Tom: No nope. Mike that section is over
you non-musical mook
Mike: Well sorry
Tom: Nevermind. I'll handle this
section myself
Talk quietly amongst yourselves
Tom: Danny Elfman, Danny Elfman
Just sounds like Danny Elfman,
Danny Elfman
It just sounds like Danny Elfman
He’s the Dad of Jenna Elfman
Jenna Elfman, Jenna Elfman
He's the daughter of Danny Elfman,
Danny Elfman
Crow: Oh say Mike
You know I didn't think
this movie was as bad as the usual fair
Mike: Oh you're joking I hope
Crow: No no no. No admittedly
it had some flaws
It's a little overzealous
pursuing some of its ideas. Granted
But, but I think it was more
a problem of form
A movie is just not the right medium
for this material it needs TV
It needs to be a series
Mike: Hmm. I dunno
Crow: Just let me pitch this to ya
Mike: Ah okay. I'm listening. Go
Crow: Great great. Thanks for hearing
me out
Okay The Final Sacrifice the series
Mike: The name goes
Crow:What?
Mike: Never liked the name.
The name goes. It's banal
Crow: But if you're hoping to connect
the series with the movie Mike
We need something like, oh, "Night Mistress"
Crow: Night Mistress
Mike: Yeah or Klootchy and the Lieutenant
Y'know something that's gonna seduce people
Really connect with them
We'll work on that
Crow: Okay okay. So you got Rowsdower
and he roams through Canada and
he's got his little pal Troy
and they all get into all kind of scrapes
but they help people
Mike: Alabama
Crow: What?
Mike: Alabama, Chicago, Cleveland
No I like Alabama. You like Alabama?
Is your show
Crow: Well to me Canada is the essence
Mike: Pittsburgh! We'll do it in Pittsburgh
Crow: Well if I supposed you actually
film it in Pittsburgh
Mike: No no no no. We film in Canada.
Have to
[intercom beep]
Hold on
Yeah, Judy
Okay, thanks
You got two minutes.
Guttenberg’s people are coming in
Crow: What do yo mean
"Guttenberg’s people are coming in"
Mike: What I mean you just
lost a minute. Go
Crow: Wow. Sorry sorry.
So the lead character is
Rowsdower of course
Mike: Lead character is the kid
Sparky McHoolahand
or whatever the hell his name was.
You like that name? I never liked that name
Crow: Well that's not his name
Mike: But I like all the funny beer stuff
you did with that Rowsdower guy
Him being a hopeless drunk and all that
He's lovable you know?
He falls down. He's sick a lot,
but he's lovable
And the kid?
Kid works in a brewery
Crow: I actually had an
hour long drama in mind
Mike: What are you, one of those
Dennis Franz freaks, huh?
Crow: Now wait a minute I think that
Mike: Wait wait wait!
Give me a second here
I'm going somewhere. I'm there I'm there.
This Rowsdower character guy
Full frontal you know?
Couple times a season
Tasteful. Low lights. Just a hint
[intercom beep]
Mike: Hold on. Yes Judy?
I know. You got 30 seconds
Crow: Okay well there's this main character
Um, Sparky
Mike: Has a friend. A girl
Hell he's a girl too. There are
a lot of girls. They're all roommates
There's a goofy girl, a serious girl, a cheerleader,
the loose girl. Everybody in
the damn series is a damn girl
Crow: Yeah, but Rowsdower
Mike: A big hairy girl!
[intercom beep]
Yes Judy? I'll tell you what
I got a show idea for you. You get
out of my office till you give me something
I can use. Now I gotta go meet
Guttenberg's people
Crow: Gee-whiz
[Tom singing]
Tom: Hey where's the music?
You guys!
The end!
Crow: Then we shall meet at midnight
and then we will
Tom: Hello Mike
Mike: Hi fellas. How's it going?
Crow: Nice flowers
Mike: Thanks
Hey!
You guys didn't take and go
and start a cult, did you?
Tom: A cult?
A cult? No of course not
Crow: That is the most absurd thing
Yeah well we did
Tom: Yeah you wanna join?
Mike: No I don't wanna join
You'll probably sacrificing black pullets
and wearing goat heads and things
Crow: Well you know we thought about all
that, but it just seemed like a lot of work
Tom: Actually we just like to bake muffins
Lots of different kinds
Crow:  Yeah then we get together
at each other's houses
and watch Ally McBeal
Tom: Or one of our collections of taped Sisters episodes
Crow: Yeah we're kind of a muffiny,
Calista Flockhart, Swoosie Kurtz kind of cult
Tom: Yeah
Crow: Um Mike
Tom: Oh boy. I think we freaked him out
Crow: Okay Mike. We strip to the waist
worship an evil emanation and lop
peoples' heads off for fun
Is that less weird?
Mike: Ah yeah. That's a little easier to take
Oh Pearl is calling
Pearl: Ah. Nelson
So glad we could join you
For you see I am about to take
a giant step forward
in my program to take over the world
one person at a time
After hours of tough negotiation
I am about to possess the mind,
the soul, the very will of this man here
What was your name again?
Carl: Carl
Pearl: Alright Carl
You've cowered at my threats,
you've relishes my rewards,
you've eaten me out of house and home
Now sign!
Carl: Certainly my liege
[cellphone rings]
Carl: Hang on. Let me get this
Yeah?
Really?
How much?
Sounds good! Thanks!
I'm sorry lady. I was just taken
over by the travelers group
Gotta run bye
Pearl: Monkey, Whitey
Bobo & Brain guy: We're on it
Pearl: I guess the
Mrs. Mr. Nice Guy approach
just ain't my style
Pearl: So very shortly now Nelson
I will rule Carl!
Carl: Untie me or you'll have to answer
to the travels group
Bobo: Give me back my food!